class Flashcard {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  Flashcard({required this.question, required this.answer});
}

List<Flashcard> quesAnsList = [
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.1?",
      answer: "India has the largest number of wild tigers in the world."),
  Flashcard(question: "Q.2", answer: "chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj"),
  Flashcard(question: "Q.3:", answer: "Sher-e-Punjab"),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.T4",
      answer:
          "Babar and Jahangir were two of the great Mughals wrote their own memories."),
  Flashcard(question: "Q.5 ?", answer: "Udham Singh"),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.What other viruses belong to the coronavirus family?",
      answer: "SARS and MERS"),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.When did WHO come into force and what is the day called?",
      answer: "7th April 1948, World Health Day"),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.What does COVID-19 stand for?",
      answer: "Coronavirus disease of 2019."),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.Which scientist was the first to discover Coronavirus?",
      answer: "June Almeida"),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q.The Taj Mahal was built during the rule of:",
      answer: "Shah Jahan"),
];
